{
    "name": ".\\Italian\\Gianluigi10.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "England",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492622721.1700666,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"l'Inghilterra\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "airport",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492622675.5233893,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"l'aeroporto\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "next",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492622727.0022602,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"prossimo\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la Spagna",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492622724.1781428,
            "question": "Given the definition \"Spain\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il bacio",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492622747.5889835,
            "question": "Given the definition \"kiss\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "dare",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492622744.9897678,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to give\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il preside",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492622718.6342754,
            "question": "Given the definition \"school, principal\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "l'affetto",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492622730.4255347,
            "question": "Given the definition \"affection, love\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to kiss",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492622751.2616127,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"baciare\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "place",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492622753.9817152,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il posto\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to pay"
            ],
            "answer": "to pay (for)",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492622782.3444843,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"pagare\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "never"
            ],
            "answer": "never, ever",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492622813.4593954,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"mai\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to give",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492622775.9689398,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"dare\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "svegliarsi",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492622823.4392812,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to wake up\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to swear",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492622792.948187,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"giurare\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "glance, look"
            ],
            "answer": "look, glance",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492622830.1192734,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"lo squardo\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il posto",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492622878.933501,
            "question": "Given the definition \"place\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "only",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492622876.1338973,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"soltanto\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to wish",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492622935.7078485,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"desiderare\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "svegliare",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492622897.1131203,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to wake\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to be able, can",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1492622956.671134,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"potere\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "piangere",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1492622962.4312131,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to cry\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to cry",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492622859.866506,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"piangere\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "departure",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492622951.9112744,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la partenza\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "portare",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492623016.9016826,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to bring\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "mancare",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1492623031.1532795,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to miss\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "money",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492622985.2184625,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"i soldi\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to love",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492623000.6058738,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"volere bene\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ultimo",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492623003.8779836,
            "question": "Given the definition \"last\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "principal"
            ],
            "answer": "school, principal",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492622979.4986672,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il preside\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "France",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492622968.6702905,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la Francia\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "potere",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492622974.3026874,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be able, can\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "presto",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492623138.2298152,
            "question": "Given the definition \"soon\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "last",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492623135.0299928,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ultimo\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "trip",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492623129.4501486,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il viaggio\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to hide",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492623140.4854724,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"nascondere\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "l'Inghilterra",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492623133.2622023,
            "question": "Given the definition \"England\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "Spain",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492623068.4600627,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la Spagna\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la Francia",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492623106.410049,
            "question": "Given the definition \"France\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "alzare",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492623108.8981187,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to lift, raise\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to call"
            ],
            "answer": "to telephone",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492623212.6396453,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"telefonare a\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "between"
            ],
            "answer": "in, between, among",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492623190.5559783,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"fra\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sad",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492623246.6031618,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"triste\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "telefonare a",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492623240.3067997,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to telephone\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "baciare",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492623263.0418072,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to kiss\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "affection, love",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492623269.9496586,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"l'affetto\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "purtroppo",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492623266.1418283,
            "question": "Given the definition \"unfortunately\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to be in a hurry",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492623204.332389,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"avere fretta\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "prossimo",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492623398.7097669,
            "question": "Given the definition \"next\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "constantly"
            ],
            "answer": "constly",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492623372.8188398,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"costoso\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "almeno",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492623391.2381346,
            "question": "Given the definition \"at least\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "above all",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1492623404.6473086,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"soprattutto\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "abbracciare",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492623323.428207,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to hug\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "at least",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492623393.7504969,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"almeno\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il viaggio",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492623303.3608189,
            "question": "Given the definition \"trip\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sorridere",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492623294.457112,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to smile\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to wake"
            ],
            "answer": "to wake up",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492623433.4250765,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"svegliarsi\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to smile",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492623485.6311505,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"sorridere\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "pagare",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492623407.1741495,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to pay (for)\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il divertimento",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492623490.2591758,
            "question": "Given the definition \"amusement, fun\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "hug",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492623411.4135187,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"l'abbraccio\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "triste",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492623456.5085125,
            "question": "Given the definition \"sad\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to hug",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492623415.149632,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"abbracciare\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "nascondere",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492623505.4509122,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to hide\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "desiderare",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492623574.12888,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to wish\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to miss",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492623569.296853,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"mancare\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "soltanto",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492623545.812669,
            "question": "Given the definition \"only\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "avere fretta",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492623532.0779727,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to be in a hurry\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "kiss",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492623519.4351256,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il bacio\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "soon",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492623522.1543562,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"presto\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "l'inizio",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492623564.2248676,
            "question": "Given the definition \"beginning\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "volere bene",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492623550.9938056,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to love\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "unfortunately",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492623654.5544353,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"purtroppo\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "costoso",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492623642.7825718,
            "question": "Given the definition \"constly\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "mai",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492623651.2626967,
            "question": "Given the definition \"never, ever\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "beginning",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492623589.0123408,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"l'inizio\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sun",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492623649.4469705,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il sole\"?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "soldi"
            ],
            "answer": "i soldi",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492623595.3401263,
            "question": "Given the definition \"money\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "l'aeroporto",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492623584.4124136,
            "question": "Given the definition \"airport\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "giurare",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492623661.1222098,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to swear\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "soprattutto",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1492623758.499448,
            "question": "Given the definition \"above all\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to bring",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492623702.5725188,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"portare\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il sole",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492623739.9717963,
            "question": "Given the definition \"sun\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to lift up"
            ],
            "answer": "to lift, raise",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492623674.0497258,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"alzare\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la partenza",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492623764.1833334,
            "question": "Given the definition \"departure\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "fra",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492623668.9703834,
            "question": "Given the definition \"in, between, among\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "lo squardo",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1492623761.4873772,
            "question": "Given the definition \"look, glance\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "l'abbraccio",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1492623729.720003,
            "question": "Given the definition \"hug\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "fun"
            ],
            "answer": "amusement, fun",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492623768.4312105,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il divertimento\"?",
            "tried": 1
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to wake",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1492623773.7988117,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"svegliare\"?",
            "tried": 1
        }
    ]
}